This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope that we'll never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm so
truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
pause, we'll reach it.
We are whole.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that I wanna take you to.
Let's head forth and.
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
Where'd Rage you go? No clue.
Guess she had something to take care of.
Black tea! Green tea!
Choose, please!
Anyway, here's a question.
Where are Sanji and his wife going to live
after this whole nutty wedding is over?
In Germa, of course.
That is to say, she's
essential to keep us a hostage.
Otherwise, who knows what
demands they'll make.
We are dealing with pirates, after all.
Nice.
You're really on top of this.
How do we know if Big Mom's
not thinking the same thing?
What if she wants to keep
Sanji as her hostage?
What the hell are you saying, Niji?
Hm?
Sanji's useless as a hostage.
Even if Big Mom does end up killing
him, would any of us give a damn?
Hmph, you're right.
Aw, how sad!
It's gonna be fun, isn't it?
Having our little brother
around like old times?
Oh, I'm so ready to eat dinner.
Look at me.
I'm full of life.
Is anybody hungry?
You must be.
I'm sorry, Blaze.
We'll put all that tender young
flesh to good use. Don't worry.
Good news!
But I'm using it right now!
I'll be so happy to shut you up!
Barrel deck your own grave.
There was too much chaos
for them to notice.
But the carrot that got captured
with me was actually a fake.
It's an animal that was transformed into a
mirror image of carrot by Brulé's ability.
A frog, I think.
The real carrot is putting on an act.
Waiting for me to make my move.
No!
This isn't fair!
Don't eat me! Please!
Help me, Cabral!
I feel bad for the frog,
but this is our only shot.
We have 16 enemies to deal with in here.
The most troubling ones are
Randolph, the Aristocroc,
And probably that chimney guy, Diesel.
Well, and Barrel, of course.
My only chance is to catch them off guard.
I'll strike the moment
they drop the fake carrot.
Okay, Randolph, cut the rope for me.
You got it.
She'll flip out once we drop her.
I gotta put the lid on right away.
Ready?
Because here I go!
Okay, Carrot, now!
Hiding up for the throw!
What are you doing down
there, Randolph? Get up!
Lady Ball!
Someone came from the attic!
Look!
What?
Why do we have two rabbit girls now?
All right!
Slow down!
I'm gonna fall!
Carrie, hurry up!
Leave it to me, chow-will!
What's she trying to do?
Don't just sit there.
Cut the damn rope, Randolph.
Right.
Carrot, no!
I'm shutting this! No!
No!
This is bad. Very bad.
Please no!
Help me!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Hot, hot, hot!
My turn!
Let's rumble!
Are you okay?
This is bad news.
That's not good!
Look what you do, Lady Brumaya!
Let's trickle, Luna!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Huh?
This got real ugly.
I better tell Mama quick.
I've got this!
Chouchou! Choo-choo-choo!
Choo-choo-choo-choo!
Suck on that, doops!
Once this train starts moving, there is
nobody in the world that can catch up to me!
Ow!
Crush! Huh?
That's who?
Are you insane?
We're going too fast!
You're doing great! No, I'm not!
Let me go, dammit! Okay!
What?
I'm gonna crash!
Even I can stop this train!
Yes!
That's all of them!
We did it!
My plan really worked!
All clear here!
Yeah, same!
Now we can use Brule's power to help us.
We can hop in and out of
any mirror we want to.
Let's start by searching
for our other friends.
We'll check the mirrors like before.
May I come in? Uh-huh.
Thanks for going shopping.
Oh, it ain't nothing, sir.
But, uh, I do have some news.
It turns out, We're holding Straw Hat and
the Cat Burglar captive in the library.
They caught Luffy and Nami?
No, don't stress out.
They don't want them
interfering with the wedding.
As long as you don't run away, the
whole situation will tidy up nicely.
All right, Sanji.
Then some of your other friends
are causing trouble in the Shit.
It says Soul King and Jaguar
Mink are going on a rampage.
Brooke.
Sweet General Smoothie and Baron Tamago
were apparently guarding the area.
Although the intruders
have eluded them thus far,
it's only a matter of
time before they, uh...
That's enough.
Can I have my groceries? Uh-huh.
Right here, sir.
If you want something really
good, might I recommend eggplant?
No, thanks.
Can I use this kitchen?
Huh?
Pudding didn't show up for dinner tonight.
I should cook her something
in case she's hungry.
Well, ain't that a thing?
She's really got me worried.
Yeah, I heard she's not feeling well.
It's a real shame, sir.
Thanks, Pedro.
We did it.
I'll crush you!
You've got some nerve
for a damn pile of bones!
Whatever it takes, my good sir!
Swallow Bandarole!
You know,
I made a rather difficult
request of my dear associate,
but now he's risking his life for me.
So I must see this to the end!
Otherwise, I'll lose
face, don't you think?
That's a joke!
I don't have a face to
lose in the first place!
Saying I'm a skeleton!
Do you get it?
Guards, can you hear me?
is the intruder in there with
my treasure mama what are
you doing down here i can handle
this Let's fight on my own.
Get out of my way, Smoothie.
Do you have any idea whose
treasure you're messing with?
Well, do you?
It can't be.
Oh my, what a perfectly
unique creature you are.
The intruder is passing through
the hallway near the courtyard now!
Move in from both sides!
All hands, raise up your shields!
And charge!
Just a little more and we've got him!
All right, now that we're in the
court, God, he's done for! Damn it.
They must be plotting something.
Ah, the memory, she comes back.
Baron Tamago.
Captain Pedro, formerly
of the Nox Pirates.
Even as mon adversaire, I must
extend you a measure of respect.
Every time I see you, I
feel that strange old ache.
And I'm sure the scar over your
left eye feels identique as mine.
So,
dites-moi, why would an homme Kuma Vice,
who held onto life so
fiercely five years back,
Return here to repeat
the same stupid mistake.
You don't have much longer
to live, mon adversaire.
After all, on that fateful day...
Mama stole away 50 years of
your life, n 'est-ce pas?
Of course, I am well aware.
I've made peace with my fate.
I'm under no illusion that
I'll make it out alive!
I don't know.
Oh no...
That was it!
Sanji?
Sorry...
Curious!
He's not here, either!
I don't know where to look!
Stop sleeping, we're late!
We're searching for a mirror
to the whole cave Shit.
Where is it?
Hey, Diesel, do you know
how this place works?
Not at all.
Let me go!
This place has access to
every mirror on the island,
so one of them must be close to Luffy.
As long as we're touching Barrel, we can
hop in and out as many times as we need to.
But at this rate, we're going
to be searching all day long.
Wake up already!
We're in a rush!
Well, there's no point
in complaining about it.
All we can do is keep looking for now.
So get ready for a long ride, Diesel!
You'll pay for this!
Just you wait!
Cut it out, Luffy!
What the heck are you thinking?
You're wasting your time.
If you don't stop that, you're
going to tear your hands off!
Nasty idea! Huh?
Loopy, stop! This is crazy!
I have to!
There's no other way for us to
get out of this stupid book!
I don't want to have my hands torn off
either, but I'll tell you one thing!
It's better than dying!
Just a little more!
Oh, they're stretched even
thinner than last time.
That's what I want.
We sit and wait for someone
to come and save us.
We'll end up losing everything we've got.
We'll sit here and suffer till Big Mom
decides to kill us, and that's stupid.
I will not die like that.
I'll do what I gotta.
You rip your hands off, too! What?
Not a chance! You're crazy!
Then let me do this my way!
Stop nagging me!
I don't want to see you
tear your own hands off!
Don't be a baby!
I am not gonna die in
a dumb place like this!
No!
Shoot, I got carried away
and made way too much.
I don't think pudding's appetite
is this big, what was I thinking?
Oh well, if she can't
finish it then I can help.
Your cooking skills are
amazing, Sanji. It's beautiful.
Why don't you have some, too? Uh-oh.
I can't possibly eat this much.
Say, ah.
Ooh, ah, yeah!
Pudding, I'm on my way.
Uh-huh?
You taking a look, Sanji, sir?
Oh, uh-huh.
I'm gonna enjoy the one and only
beam of light that's left in my life.
I got you.
You want an eggplant for the road?
Never know. I'm good.
Stryhat and the Cat-Burgler are
already in notre possession.
You may as well surrender.
May as well kick your ass.
Uh, un combat a la mort, d 'accord!
It's some anti-mink
technologique, one might say.
Planned ahead, I see. Oh, hey, hey.
I'm wearing tights that protect
me from laser-tax-electrique.
A pair of tights won't stop me.
I'll settle this grudge.
That must be the whole cake Shit. Oh, hey.
Prince Peckham's. Pedro! Zippo!
I can't believe it!
I missed you! Got you! Got you!
Got you! Got you.
Where are you, Karoo, here?
Get out!
I'm a member of the Big Mom Pirates now!
This is where I live, obviously!
Solo!
You'll lose more than an eye this time!
A close shave.
My eye still leaks from
time to time, you know.
As if it records the pain of
being stabbed by your blade.
What Shigure faced that day was nothing.
Look at you dirty thieves.
What a mess you've made.
No!
I'll be taking a hundred
years of your life.
Fight it, Zippo! Please!
Oh, no. Zippo!
Why did it come to this?
That wasn't nearly enough.
He didn't have a hundred years.
It seems he only had 30 left in his
useless life too bad that means somebody
else needs to pay the rest that falls
on you since you're his partner,
naughty boy now!
I'll be taking those 70 years.
Let's hope you have enough.
Have mercy, mama!
He was like a big brother to me.
70 years is too much.
There's nothing short of a death sentence.
Stop it!
This is pathetic!
I'm flagging you, mama!
Enough.
Don't cry.
I get it.
10 years, then I'll take
10 years off his debt.
No more—that's all the mercy I have
for the man who took Tomago's eye.
Your
price is 60 years.
Not
generous enough for you, Peckham's dear!
dear
Mama, I...
Hey, big mom
How many years will this eye spare me?
I can't die just yet.
The dawn of the new world is coming soon.
I can't rest until I've seen it.
Ma-ma-ma-ma.
Well, aren't you a charmer?
I'll make it 50 years then.
Enjoy the rest of your life.
Ex-Benedict!
A rescue Lancor. No answer!
Why would you dare to return here?
Why relive the nightmare
of your companion's
demise over the day you
lost 50 years of your life?
To help the Straw Hats.
How else could I repay
them for saving my home?
More than that,
I believe that they will bring forth the
new world that I have
dreamt of for so long.
Pedro, the dawn of a new
day will come to this world.
They will surpass you, Karoo.
The Straw Hats will be the
heralds of a bright new age.
Ha!
They have already been dealt with.
What do you expect those
fools to accomplish?
This is all Cake Island, n 'est-ce pas?
Yeah, so what?
I believe in the Straw Hats.
That's the choice I made.
Therefore, the meager time that I have
left in this world, I offer to them!
them.
Make no mistake, Tamago.
I won't die here.
I refuse to lay down
this sword until their
mission here is complete
my
fight
isn't over no
means no lover boy pack
it up why not Because
Lady Pudding would like
her privacy go away.
What could she be doing?
Please, just give this to her.
Don't make me slam in your face.
Wait a minute.
I think there's a
balcony outside her room.
I'll pass it through the window.
Maybe I shouldn't.
She might think I'm peeping.
What am I thinking?
We're going to be husband
and wife tomorrow.
I'll be seeing that sort
of thing all the time.
Nothing wrong with getting a sneak peek.
Good.
She's well enough to laugh, at least.
There's my sweet little pudding.
Who is she talking to?
Reizhou?
What's she doing here?
Why's pudding with her?
You cannot honestly be that naive.
You think I'd marry
that lowlife pirate? Ha!
You must be out of your freaking mind.
Not a chance in hell.
I'm one of Mama's favorites, you know.
Especially because of my acting.
In fact, she cares for me so much.
It's almost overbearing.
Fulsome stupid man from time to
time in the old bag is happy.
And it was almost too easy
tricking the Straw Hats.
Only my closest family knows
what my true nature really is.
A little more!
What a ruckus.
This is going on for far too long. Never!
You have to stop.
You really will rip your arms off.
I'm going to make her pay.
Whatever the cost.
But you don't have to worry.
I decided I will not marry him.
Listen.
The reason why we're not getting married.
Is because that love—lorn fool
played right into my hands.
And
during the wedding ceremony.
I
plan to shoot him full of holes.
And
as for you too.
You're not leaving this
place alive either.
either
Hey, Pudding, wait!
Is this a joke?
Well, goodbye, you miserable little rats.
What monster?
She was setting us up
to fail from the get-go!
Why is she doing this to Sanji?
It's so screwed up!
You people are so gullible!
And Germa 666 is supposed
to be an evil army!
Keep living in your
fantasy world, you twits!
You deserve this!
Mama only wants two things from you.
Your vast army of clone soldiers.
And your scientific technology.
Do you always listen to mommy?
My such defiance.
That is exactly why we don't
need you the entirety of the
Germa kingdom is anchored
within our borders right now,
like flies drawn to rotting fruit.
The political marriage was meant
to entice you; it works so well.
You took the bait just as mama planned!
And at the wedding tomorrow,
the entire Vin Smoke
family will be eliminated.